[Bloomberg the Company & Its ProductsThe Company & its Products](https://www.bloomberg.com/company/?utm_source=bloomberg-menu&utm_medium=notices)[Bloomberg Terminal Demo Request](https://www.bloomberg.com/professional/contact-menu/?utm_source=bloomberg-menu&utm_medium=notices&bbgsum=DG-WS-PROF-DEMO-bbgmenu)[Bloomberg Anywhere Remote LoginBloomberg Anywhere Login](https://bba.bloomberg.net/?utm_source=bloomberg-menu&utm_medium=notices)[Bloomberg Customer SupportCustomer Support](https://www.bloomberg.com/professional/support/?utm_source=bloomberg-menu&utm_medium=notices)

* ### Bloomberg
    
    Connecting decision makers to a dynamic network of information, people and ideas, Bloomberg quickly and accurately delivers business and financial information, news and insight around the world
    
    ### For Customers

    ### Support
    
    Americas+1 212 318 2000
    
    EMEA+44 20 7330 7500
    
    Asia Pacific+65 6212 1000
    
* ### Company

    ### Communications

    ### Follow

* ### Products

    ### Industry Products

* ### Media

    ### Media Services

* ### Company

    ### Communications

    ### Follow

* ### Products

    ### Industry Products

* ### Media
    
    * [Bloomberg  
        Technology](https://www.bloomberg.com/technology/?utm_source=bloomberg-menu&utm_medium=notices)
    * [Bloomberg  
        Businessweek](https://www.bloomberg.com/businessweek/?utm_source=bloomberg-menu&utm_medium=notices)
    
    ### Media Services

* ### Bloomberg
    
    Connecting decision makers to a dynamic network of information, people and ideas, Bloomberg quickly and accurately delivers business and financial information, news and insight around the world
    
    ### For Customers

    ### Support
    
    Americas+1 212 318 2000
    
    EMEA+44 20 7330 7500
    
    Asia Pacific+65 6212 1000

  [Bloomberg Notices and Policies](https://www.bloomberg.com/notices) Menu

Privacy
=======

**Last Updated: April 18, 2024**

Table of Contents
-----------------

[Accuracy, Security, And Retention Of Your Personal Information](#accuracy-security-and-retention-of-your-personal-information)

Bloomberg L.P. and its [affiliates](https://www.bloomberg.com/notices/notices-and-policies/colombia/) (together “Bloomberg”) respects the privacy rights of our users and is strongly committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to this website, any newsletters subscribed to via this website, digital subscriptions to Bloomberg.com and Bloomberg Businessweek, information collected when you subscribe to the print edition of Bloomberg Businessweek, and any other service or product of Bloomberg, including other websites, mobile applications, or other digital properties, as expressly indicated by Bloomberg such as through a link or other display of this Privacy Policy (collectively, “this Site”).

If you are a California resident, refer to the Privacy Policy’s [California Section](#california) for more information.

If you are a Republic of Korea resident, please [click here to see the Privacy Policy for that country](https://www.bloomberg.com/notices/privacy/privacy-korea/).

Collection And Use Of Your Personal Information
-----------------------------------------------

Bloomberg, or where relevant a designated service provider, collects personal information that you choose to provide or we receive from other sources. This may include personal information you provide through this Site, on third-party websites and applications when subscribing digitally to Bloomberg.com or Bloomberg Businessweek, through registering for our services and products, through requesting certain Bloomberg services or products, by submitting the information to enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion or offline in connection with your Bloomberg Businessweek print edition subscription.

We and designated service providers, may obtain the following types of personal information in connection with this Site:

* Name, email address, postal address, account names and passwords, or other contact information
* Signature, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, or other similar identifiers
* Professional, industry, employment-related, or education information
* Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, preferences, and information regarding a user’s interaction (including reading habits) with an Internet website, application, and/or advertisements, which also includes a user’s interactions through heatmaps and session replay.
* Demographic information
* Billing information, credit card number or other financial information, which may include personal financial information if submitted by you in a survey on the Site
* Geolocation
* Audio, electronic, visual or similar information
* Inferences drawn from the personal information identified above to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences and behavior

Personal information is obtained directly from you, from others authorized to provide the information, from activity on the Site, and from other parties with whom we work, such as service providers, business partners, advertisers, advertising technology providers, advertising servers, data analytics providers, and social networks. If you submit personal information about others, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to do so and that you have received authorization from the person about whom you are providing the information and that person has consented to have all information used, disclosed, and transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to link your social media or other third-party accounts to our services, we may obtain your personal information from these sources. You may disconnect this link at any time by visiting your account page on these third-party platforms or the settings page of your mobile device.

We use this information for carefully considered business purposes which also benefit our customers and which include some or all of the following:

* to provide and facilitate our services and products
* to operate our services, products, and systems properly
* to communicate with you
* to help Bloomberg improve, upgrade, or enhance our services and products and develop new services and products
* to provide support for our services and products
* to maintain the quality and safety of products and services, and for internal quality control purposes, including debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality
* to provide you with offers and promotions about services and products of Bloomberg or of other parties that may be of interest to you
* to create a “lookalike audience” or “matched audience” of (prospective) customers for targeted advertising on social media platforms
* to enhance your experience with this Site, including to save your preferences and login information, create hashed identifiers that can be used to help us identify you on our site and third-party sites, provide customized content or contextual advertisements, and provide tailored advertisements on our site and third-party sites
* to analyze website usage, analyze use of this Site, and analyze and measure ad impressions
* to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Bloomberg or others and to monitor compliance with and enforce the terms of any agreement with Bloomberg
* to monitor to detect security incidents and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and hold those responsible for that activity

You may instruct Bloomberg at any time not to use your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy to provide you with offers and promotions by clicking [here](https://www.bloomberg.com/email-settings/manage/) or through your account settings by clicking [here](https://login.bloomberg.com/signup). Please note that if you exercise choice in this manner, you will continue to receive communications concerning your account and products and services you requested, and in response to any requests for information by you. Please also note that this opt-out process may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law. To update your settings for receiving offers and promotions from Bloomberg Industry Group, please click [here](https://www.bloombergindustry.com/privacy-policy/).

Use Of Cookies And Other Electronic Technologies
------------------------------------------------

Bloomberg and the parties with whom we work (e.g., service providers, business partners, advertisers, ad technology providers and advertising servers) may place, view, and/or use “cookies”, web server logs, web beacons, pixels or other electronic technologies to collect statistical and other information about you and your use of this Site. This information may include information about the IP address of your computer, browser type, language, operating system, your mobile device, device ID, geolocation data, the state or country from which you accessed this Site’s services, the webpages visited, the date and the time of a visit, the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting this Site, the number of links you click within this Site, the functions you use on this Site, the databases you view and the searches you request on this Site, the types of articles you read, the data you save or download from this Site and the number of times you view an advertisement.

Bloomberg and the parties with whom we work may use the information collected for various reasons, either on behalf of Bloomberg or for the other parties’ own purposes, including research, analysis, to better serve visitors to this Site (such as by enabling log-in, providing access to certain sections of this Site, providing customized content or customized contextual advertisements, or presenting online advertising on this Site or other websites tailored to your interests as described further below), to compile aggregate and anonymous information about usage of this Site and other websites, other statistics, etc. However, if you have deleted and disabled cookies, these uses will not be possible to the extent they are based on cookie information. To opt out of Google Analytics please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). To opt out of Parse.ly analytics, please click [here](http://srv.config.parsely.com/optout). We also use Microsoft Clarity to capture how you use and interact with our Services. Microsoft Clarity uses cookies to capture this information. For more information on Microsoft Clarity, visit the [Microsoft privacy statement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-US/privacystatement).

To assist us with the uses described in this Privacy Policy, information collected about you and your use of this Site or other websites may be aggregated, analyzed or combined with personal or other information about you from other online or offline sources. If you prefer that we not combine non-personal information that has been collected, through cookies, about your use of this Site or other websites with personal or other information about you, then please delete and disable cookies for each browser, on each computer you use to surf the Web.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to disable cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Likewise, most mobile devices allow you to disable the ability for geolocation information to be collected from your mobile device. The help function on most browsers and mobile devices contains instructions on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies, disable cookies entirely, or disable the collection of geolocation data. You need to set each browser, on each device you use to surf the Web. Thus, if you use multiple browsers (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.), you should repeat this procedure with each one. Similarly, if you connect to the Web from multiple devices (e.g., work and home), you need to set each browser on each device. Depending on your jurisdiction, you may be able to utilize additional cookie management tools. However, if you disable certain cookies or refuse to accept a request to place a cookie, it is possible that some parts of this Site, such as the polls, surveys, contests, and product sales, and certain areas of this Site for which you need to log in, will not function properly, and the advertising you receive when you visit this Site may not be advertisements tailored to your interests.

Advertisements
--------------

Bloomberg, its designated service providers, or third-party advertisers or their advertising servers may also place or recognize unique cookies on your computer or use other electronic technologies in order to help display advertisements that you see on this Site or on other websites. Information about your visits to, and activity on, this Site and other websites, an IP address, the number of times you have viewed an advertisement, your interests and preferences and other such usage information is used, alone or in combination with other information, to create aggregate groups of users and to display advertisements that may be of particular interest to you or a group of users with similar interests to you. We may use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising and product performance. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this Site, and to learn which banner ads bring users to this Site. The use and collection of your information by third-party service providers, and third-party advertisers and their advertising servers is not covered by this Privacy Policy. Bloomberg adheres to the industry’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising located [here](http://www.aboutads.info/principles). To “opt out” of advertising cookies placed by participating companies in the Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising, and thereby limit the tracking of your online activity and the targeted advertising you receive, please click [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) for browsers and click [here](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) for mobile devices. To “opt out” of advertising cookies placed by the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) online behavioral advertising member networks, and thereby limit the tracking of your online activity and the targeted advertising you receive, please click [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) for browsers and click [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice/) for mobile devices. To opt out of advertising cookies for Your Online Choices if you are based in the EU, please click [here](http://youronlinechoices.eu/).

In addition, as stated above, we may use your personal information to enhance your experience on our Site and other sites. In order to accomplish this, we may share information about you along with a hashed version of your email address or phone number with third-party advertising companies so that they and we can facilitate customized ad campaigns and other offers on our Site and on other platforms. “Hashing” transforms your email into an unrecognizable series of numbers and letters (e.g. a “hashed” version of jane@email.com would bek5f7g23@email.com). You may opt out by clicking [here](https://www.bloomberg.com/feedback/datainquiry/) and also by using the designated “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” tool within Bloomberg digital properties.

Some third party websites and platforms also allow you to manage the collection and use of your information for advertising purposes. Google Ad Manager, Google Analytics for Display Advertising, and other designated service providers assist Bloomberg with advertisement display functions and related analytics for this Site. To opt out of tailored advertising from Google tracking technologies, please click [here](https://adssettings.google.com/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCgS9lVg728TWSpeD-44vTykgKBRgPEIXMhJXrobSAyGFPr_Bz5e1NKtCQfqe0WhV2pY6yenQKZF3wRYCBSrfyDCTqvLE9bqQLIKWtcbN0j9VLfpYt4&hl=en).

Note that even if you exercise choice for targeted advertising, you will still receive online advertising, but the advertisements will be more general in nature. You may still continue to see targeted advertising if you do not opt out via the designated methods and/or if you wish to remain a subscriber.

Disclosure Of Your Personal Information
---------------------------------------

Bloomberg may disclose the personal information described above with our affiliates and designated service providers, for the business purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Bloomberg may also disclose to third parties, including advertising networks, data analytics providers and social networks, your use of our or other websites, including online identifiers, Internet Protocol address, and Internet or other electronic network activity information, and the services provided by us for the business purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Bloomberg may disclose your personal information (excluding security photographs or video) with a sponsor or other third party (“Third-Party Provider”) that provides you with offers or promotions that may be of interest to you. You may instruct Bloomberg at any time not to share your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy with such Third-Party Providers by clicking [here and submitting your email address and selecting “Bloomberg on Behalf of Select Partners”](https://www.bloomberg.com/email-settings/manage). Please note that (i) this opt-out process may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law; and (ii) even after such opt-out process is completed, your personal information may continue to be shared with our affiliates (including affiliated websites under common ownership or control) and designated service providers.

Bloomberg may also disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with any applicable law, rule, or regulation, or in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process, subject to [Bloomberg’s Law Enforcement Data Request Statement](https://www.bloomberg.com/notices/law-enforcement/); (b) protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Bloomberg or others; (c) monitor compliance with and enforce any terms of service on this Site; (d) provide our services and products (including allowing a purchaser of Bloomberg or a Bloomberg division to continue to serve you); (e) perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection; (f) provide you with offers, promotions or advertisements from Bloomberg; or (g) operate the systems that provide our services and products properly.

If you participate in certain features of this Site (e.g., sharing news stories of interest), please note that any information you or others voluntarily disclose through use of these features, becomes available to the public and/or other users whom you have designated. If you choose to provide access to designated individuals, please be aware that any information you post will be visible to such individuals for their use. Bloomberg is not responsible for the information that you or others choose to disclose publicly on this Site, and neither Bloomberg’s nor others’ use of such information is subject to this Privacy Policy.

The collection, further use, and/or disclosure of your information by Third-Party Providers or by other third parties is not the responsibility of Bloomberg. Rather, such collection, use, and/or disclosure is governed by the third parties’ privacy policies.

Accuracy, Security, And Retention Of Your Personal Information
--------------------------------------------------------------

Any personal information you provide to Bloomberg is kept on secure servers. Bloomberg uses security measures appropriate to the provision of the relevant product or service, such as reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures (a) that are designed to safeguard personal information against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification; and (b) to ensure the integrity of the personal information. To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of the logon ID and password you may have set up in connection with your participation in this Site’s services. Personal information is retained for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) described in this Privacy Policy, or as may be permitted under applicable law. For example, personal information is retained if the information is reasonably necessary to manage your relationship with us or to provide our products and services to you.  To determine the appropriate retention period, we will generally consider the following criteria: the length of time needed to achieve the purpose your information was collected for; whether you ceased using our services or products; the existence of any relevant legal proceedings; or applicable legal and regulatory requirements.

Rights With Respect To Your Personal Information
------------------------------------------------

Depending on the jurisdiction, you may have the following rights with respect to your personal information:

* To access and request certain information about the processing of your personal information
* To obtain a portable copy of your personal information
* To correct personal information
* To delete personal information
* To restrict processing of certain personal information
* To object to the processing of personal information
* To withdraw consent, where this was the lawful reason for processing
* To lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority

Please bear in mind that if you exercise such rights this may affect our ability to provide our products and services.

To exercise a right related to your personal information, please contact us by clicking [here](http://www.bloomberg.com/datainquiry) or by e-mailing us at [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com). While Bloomberg will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request, we also reserve the right to impose certain restrictions and requirements on such requests, if allowed or required by applicable laws. In the event that we cannot take action with respect to a request relating to your personal information, in certain jurisdictions, you may have the right to appeal that decision by e-mailing us at [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com).

Please note that it may take some time to process your request, consistent with applicable law.

If you choose to exercise these rights, we may ask that you provide sufficient information, including the products and services you have used in the past, your state and country of residence, and contact information, in order for us to verify your identity and process your request. Depending on the types of requests, we may ask for additional information.

You may use an authorized agent to submit a request on your behalf related to your personal information. If you choose to use an authorized agent, you should supply your agent with written permission to act on your behalf in relation to your request, and your agent must provide us with proof of such authorization before we process your request.

California
----------

If you are a California resident, the information below applies to you and supplements the information provided above.

Certain information collected on this Site, including your log-in and password, may constitute “sensitive personal information” as that term is defined by the California privacy law. However, Bloomberg only uses such information to provide our services and products or as otherwise permitted under California privacy law.

While we do not “sell” your personal information in exchange for money or “share” your personal information for cross-context behavioral or targeted advertising outside of the use of electronic technologies to provide relevant advertisements, to the extent that certain practices described above relating to advertising constitute targeted advertising, or are considered “selling” or “sharing” under California privacy law, you may adjust your preferences by using the designated tool within Bloomberg’s digital properties. You may also submit a request by selecting the “Do Not Sell/ or Share My Personal Information” option in this [form to opt out future sales in other contexts](https://www.bloomberg.com/feedback/datainquiry/).

If you choose to exercise these rights set out in this Privacy Notice, you also have a right not to receive discriminatory treatment for exercising your rights.

To opt-out of further “sales” or “sharing” of your personal information by downstream participants in tailored advertising who are signatories to the IAB Privacy, LLC’s Limited Service Provider Agreement (LSPA), please click  and opt out on the listed digital property of the downstream participant. Additionally, where recognized, we treat global privacy control signals as a request to opt-out of the “sale” or “sharing” of personal information.

Additionally, certain browser plug-ins provide options for communicating opt-out preference signals such as global privacy control.  Where recognized, we treat global privacy control signals as a request to opt-out of the “sale” or “sharing” of personal information.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Bloomberg L.P. to its affiliates and/or third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email with your first name, last name, mailing address, email address and telephone number to [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com). Please include “California Privacy Rights” in the Subject line of your email.

You may also make such a request by writing to us at:

Bloomberg L.P.  
Attn: Legal Department  
731 Lexington Avenue  
New York, NY 10022

The Site is intended for a general audience and is not directed at children under the age of 16, nor do we have actual knowledge that we “sell” or “share” the personal information of children under the age of 16. If you have knowledge that a child under the age of 16 has submitted personal information to us, we request that you contact us via one of the methods listed above so that we may delete the information.

Transfer Of Your Personal Information To Other Countries
--------------------------------------------------------

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Privacy Policy may involve the transfer and processing of your personal information to and in various countries that may have different levels of privacy protection than your country. By using our products and services, you acknowledge and agree to such transfers and processing, including to and in the United States. We implement appropriate safeguards to protect such personal information, which may include (without limitation) European Commission approved standard contractual clauses, to protect your personal information that is transferred. Bloomberg’s Intra-Group Personal Data Protection Statement provides additional information about Bloomberg’s personal data protection, security and transfer practices and explains how those practices ensure there are appropriate safeguards in place to protect personal information and is available [here](https://www.bloomberg.com/notices/iga-statement/).

Links To Third-Party Services
-----------------------------

Bloomberg may provide links or access to third-party websites or other digital properties, including social networking websites. Since we do not control third-party digital properties and are not responsible for any information you may provide while on such digital properties, we encourage you to read the privacy policies on those websites before providing any of your information on such digital properties.

Questions Regarding This Privacy Policy
---------------------------------------

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@bloomberg.com](mailto:privacy@bloomberg.com). Please include “Privacy” in the subject line of your inquiry. If you have complaints about Bloomberg’s processing of your personal information, you may have the right to contact the applicable supervisory authority.

Modifications To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------------

Bloomberg reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by indicating revisions through the “Last Updated” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

© 2024 Bloomberg L.P. All Rights Reserved.
